<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Berkeley Carillon Guild</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2024-05-13T17:23:18-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>9th Berkeley Carillon Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/11/festival/"/>
   <updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2023/08/11/festival</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We will be hosting the 9th Berkeley Carillon Festival on August 12-13, 2023. With recitals at noon and 2pm on both Saturday and Sunday, this is our way to celebrate new and long-standing members of our extended carillon community at Berkeley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View the program &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bXZ-jYu9cVuY2Qp_ZZO_OUyRh1kfDrAw/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to read about our upcoming music and performers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opening recital (August 12, noon) will be performed by Brunston Poon (Assistant Carillonist), Erika Anderson (Associate Carillonist), &amp;amp; Peter Trost (Associate Carillonist).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our recital of duets (August 12, 2pm) will be performed by a number of our invited recitalists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Berkeley summer celebratory recital (August 13, noon) will be performed by Abby Pan (C), Simone Browne (C), Arman Arbab (UC Berkeley alumnus), and UC Berkeley student carillonists Anna Zhao, Michelle Pan, &amp;amp; Tim Yang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The closing recital (August 13, 2pm) will be performed by Jeff Davis (University Carillonist), Dave Hunsberger (Assistant Carillonist), &amp;amp; Wesley Arai (University Carillonist, UCSB).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>GCNA Congress 2023</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/06/14/congress/"/>
   <updated>2023-06-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2023/06/14/congress</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 80th annual GCNA Congress was held at St. Stephen&amp;#39;s Church in Cohasset, Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Berkeley, Erika Anderson, Peter Trost, Brunston Poon, and Anna Zhao were in attendance, as were Jeff Davis, the University Carillonist, and Dave Hunsberger, Assistant Carillonist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter passed his GCNA Carillonneur examination and was voted into the membership, and will be an Associate Carillonist at Berkeley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erika Anderson (Associate Carillonist) performed Margo Halsted&amp;#39;s Nocturne and Joey Brink&amp;#39;s Starlight, and Erika &amp;amp; Brunston Poon (recently appointed Assistant Carillonist) performed Brink&amp;#39;s dance beneath the moon duet during the Congress&amp;#39; Twilight Concert.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>GCNA Congress 2022</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/06/12/congress/"/>
   <updated>2022-06-12T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2022/06/12/congress</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 79th annual GCNA Congress was held at the University of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Berkeley, Erika Anderson, Brunston Poon, Assistant Carillonist Dave Hunsberger, and alumni Leslie Chan, Kunal Marwaha, &amp;amp; Arman Arbab were in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erika passed her GCNA Carillonneur examination and was voted into the membership, and will be an Associate Carillonist at Berkeley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brunston performed Jeff Davis&amp;#39; When Spring was Winter and the Morning and Day movements of Vladyslav Nazarchuk&amp;#39;s Times of Day cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
